#### Contact

+34 661 77 67 03 (Mobile) segundojuanok@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/segundojuan (LinkedIn)

www.segu.work/ (Personal) github.com/JSegundo (Portfolio) www.segu.work/ (Personal)

### Top Skills

Docker

Redis

Design patterns

### Certifications

Curso de Node.js: Base de Datos con MongoDB y WebSockets

Curso de Backend con Node.js: API REST con Express.js

Full Stack Developer Program

Curso de Backend con NestJS

Developing on AWS

# Segundo Juan

Fullstack developer | React | Node | AWS

Porto, Porto, Portugal

### Summary

From building startup products from scratch to maintaining complex systems, I'm learning to balance rapid development with systematic problem-solving.

Core experience in Node.js, React, and TypeScript. I enjoy tackling complex debugging challenges and making codebases more maintainable.

## Experience

Critical TechWorks
Node.js developer
May 2024 - Present (1 year 4 months)
Oporto, Portugal

Working on maintaining Spotify's integration for BMW in-car entertainment systems.

Ourworld Meta Frontend developer April 2023 - January 2024 (10 months) Spain

Development and maintenance of two platforms (PWA and backoffice panel)
 using React + TypeScript

Ceibo Digital
Full-stack Developer
July 2022 - April 2023 (10 months)
España

- Developed diverse front-end interfaces using React, Next.js, Material-UI, Bootstrap, or plain HTML, CSS & JavaScript.
- CRUDs and third party API integration in a backend tool using Nodejs and MySQL

## Education

Plataforma 5 - Coding Bootcamp

Full stack developer, Web development · (January 2022 - April 2022)